Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Records WAG.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1944-2006
  - Series II: Bargaining Files and Related Arbitration Cases, 1938-1996
    - City of New York Department of Welfare v. Local 371 re: Welfare Department Clerks, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - City-Wide Bargaining Proposals, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Clarifications on Disputes, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining for Assistant Directors, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Collective Bargaining in Social Work(revised), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Collective Bargaining Programs for Fall Negotiations, Sep 17, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Collective Bargaining Program: November 1966 Proposal and backup materials (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Committee for a Solid Contract: Alternatives to Layoffs and Budget Cuts, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Contract: City of NY and District Council 37 et al, Clerical-Administrative Employees, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Contract: City of NY and District Council 37 et al, Social Service Employees, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Contract: City of NY and District Council 37 et al, Social Service Employees, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Contract: City of NY and Health and Hospitals Corp. et al. (proposed for Jul 1, 1987-Sep 30, 1990), May 23, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Contract: City of NY and related public employees and SSEU Local 371 and other affiliated locals, Jan 1, 1974-Dec 31, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Contract: City of NY and Senior Social Service Administrators Association, May 21, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Contract: City of NY and SSEU, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Contract: City of NY and SSEU, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Contract: City of NY and SSEU (Proposed 1969-1970), Oct 28, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Contract: City of NY and SSEU, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Contract: City of NY and SSEU Local 371 covering Model Cities Titles, Jul 1, 1974-Jun 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Contract: City of NY and SSEU Local 371, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Contract: City of NY and SSEU Local 371, Human Resources job titles, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Contract: City of NY and Welfare Local 371, Jun 4, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Contract: City-Wide between City of New York and District Council 37 for Jul 1, 1967-Jun 30, 1970, Apr 19, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Contract: City-Wide, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Contract: Draft of 1984-1987 Social Service and Related Titles, Jul 10, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Contract: Employees Union and SSEU Local 371, Dec 1, 1971-Dec 1, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Contract: Housing and Development Administration (HDA) (Proposed), Jul 1, 1976-Jun 30, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Contract: Housing and Development Administration Employees in the Repair Title Series (Proposed), Jul 1, 1974-Jun 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Contract: Social Services Local 371, Jan 1, 1966-Dec 31, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Contract: Welfare Department, May 11, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Contract Compliance/Enforcement, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Demands, Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Demands, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Demands, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Demands, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Demands, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Demands, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Demands, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Demands, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Demands, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Demands: Adult Services Administration, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Demands: Case Aide Contract, 1968-1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Demands: DC 37 City-Wide, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Demands: Family Day Care, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Demands: Human Resources Administration (HRA), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Demands: Institutional Aids, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Demands: Investigators, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Demands: Recommendations of the Impartial Chairman of the Workload and Reorganization Committee, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Demands: Reorganization and Workload Committee, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Demands: SSEU Local 371, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Demands: SSEU Local 371 and Associated District Council 37 Locals, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Demands: Union Questionnaire, Aug 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Dental Assistants' Collective Bargaining Program, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Department of Welfare Supervisory Unit (references Welfare Local 371, et al v. Dept. of Welfare, Case No. R- 45-58, 1959, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 2-70, Docket No. RU-95-69, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 42-70, Docket No. RU-123-69, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 47-70, Docket No. RU-168-70, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 48-70, Docket No. RU-169-70, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 55-73, Docket No. RU-363-73, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 67-69, Docket No. RU-81-68, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 70-69 Docket No. RU-134-69, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 71-79 Docket No. RU-135-69, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 73-70, Docket No. RU-175-70, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. B-6-73, Docket No. BCB-131-72, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 1-72, Docket No. RU-260-B-71, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No.3-72, Docket No. RU-270-71, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York: Decision No. 9-71, Docket No. RU-129-69, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 11-72, Docket No. RU-280-71, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 17-71, Docket Nos. RU-196-70, RU-197-70, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 17-72, Docket No. RU-304-72, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 18-71, Docket Nos. RU-196-70, RU-197-70, RU-218-70, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 19-72, Docket No. RU-309-72 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 20-72, Docket Nos. RU-292-71, RU-293-71, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 21-72, Docket No. RU-287-71, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 26-72, Docket Nos. RU-305-72, RU-305-72, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No, 27-71, Docket No. RU-243-70, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision Nos. 31-A-71, 31-A-72, Docket Nos. RU-206-70, RU-237-70, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 48-71, Docket No. RU-259-71, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 49-70, Docket No. RU-167-70, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 52-71, Docket No. RU-260-71, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 56-73, Docket No. RU-373-73, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 63-71, Docket No. RU-267-71, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 66-71, Docket No. RU-271-71, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 67-73, Docket Nos. RU-386-73, RU-388-73, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 74-71, Docket No. RU-253-71, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - District Council 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 78-71, Docket Nos. RU-197B-70, RU-242-70, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - District Council 37 v. Office of Labor Relations, City of New York: Decision No. B-16-71, Docket No. BCB-78-70, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - District Council 37, AFSCME: Final Signature Draft of 1995 Coalition Agreement, Mar 1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Division of Education and Rehabilitation (DER) Caseworker's Collective Bargaining Program: Draft, Aug 1966 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Draft Materials for Discussion (annotated copies), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Draft of Contract Covering Addiction Service Agency, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Draft Text of Preliminary Agreement, Jun 30, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Education Fund, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Equity Panel Decision on Employee Compensation, Sep 13, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fact-Finding Panel, 1965, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Facts in Support of Lower Workloads, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Grievance Procedures: Basic Documents for Collective Bargaining, 1963, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Haber, Herbert as Director of Labor Relations of the City of NY v. SSEU: Transcript for Case No. BCB-22-68, Dec 3, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Haber, Herbert as Director of Labor Relations of the City of NY v. SSEU: Transcript for Case No. BCB-22-68, Dec 4, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Haber, Herbert as Director of Labor Relations of the City of NY v. SSEU: Verified Petition, Verified Answer, Affidavits, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Handwritten notes referred to as "scrap notes", 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Handwritten notes referred to as "scrap notes", 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Handwritten notes referred to as "scrap notes", 1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Home Economist's Collective Bargaining Program: Drafts, Nov 1964, Aug 1966, Nov 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Homemaker's Collective Bargaining Program, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Homemaking Center: Draft Bargaining Program, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Hospital Care Investigator Collective Bargaining Program, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Hospital Care Settlement, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Items not resolved in Collective Bargaining, Apr 13, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Leaflets, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Local 456, Office and Professional Employees International Union and DC 37 v. City of New York and Related Public Employers: Decision No. 7-72, Docket No. RU-302-72, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Mage, Judith et al v. Henry Shemin, Commission of Labor: Index No. 20070/1966 (Representative Election) (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Medical Social Workers Collective Bargaining Program, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Meeting of Action Committee, Title Representatives, Executive Committee List, Jul 10, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Meeting Notices, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Memorandum(s), 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Memorandum: Procedures, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Memorandum(s) of Agreement, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Memorandum of Understanding, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Memorandum of Understanding with Respect to Unresolved Issues, Jul 1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Municipal Association of Electronic Data Processing Personnel and Local 371 v. New York City Department of Social Services: Docket Nos. R-44-67, R-48-67, Decision No. 20-68, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Negotiating Committee/Team, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Negotiating Sessions, Jan 1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Negotiations, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Negotiations: Handwritten Notes, Jan 1967 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Non Residence Welfare Center Agreement, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Offers, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Office of Collective Bargaining Public Hearing on Proposed Rules, Dec 20, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Office of Labor Relations of the City of New York v. DC 37: Decision No. B-14-71, Docket No. BCB-97-71 (A-165-71), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Petitions Calling for Special Membership Meeting on Dec 12, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Press Releases, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Program Policy Meetings, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Proposals, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Proposals, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Proposals, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Proposals: Investigator Positions, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Proposals on Reorganization, Jan 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Proposed Contract between City of New York and District Council 37 and Local 371, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Proposed Contract Summary, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Proposed Eleventh Social Services and Related Titles Contract, Jul 1, 1987-Sep 30, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Proposed Thirteenth Social Services and Related Titles Contract Demands, Jan 1, 1992-Dec 31, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Proposed Supplementary Contract between City of New York and Local 371, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Queens Report to Negotiations, Feb 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire for Bargaining Distributed to Staff Dec 7, with Results, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Questionnaire for Collective Bargaining, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Questionnaires: Specialized Welfare Centers, [1966], 1967? (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Research Material on Children's Counselor Titles for 1967-1968 Bargaining Contract, 1955-1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Salary Demands, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Salary Differential for Educational Credits, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Senior Children's Counselor's Collective Bargaining Program (Draft), Sep 1966 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - SSEU v. Department of Welfare: Case No: R-85-64, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - SSEU v. The City of New York: Case No. E68-2, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - SSEU v. The City of New York: Case No. E68-9, Knight-Fernandes, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - SSEU v. The City of New York: Docket No. R-109-67, Decision Nos. 37-68, 51-68, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - SSEU, Local 371 v. The City of New York: Decision No. 55-69, Docket Nos. RU-100-69, RU-101-69 (RU-100-B-69), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - SSEU, Local 371 v. The City of New York: Decision No. 64-69, Docket No. RU-132-69, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Staff Assignments and Transfers: Draft, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Supervisors' Collective Bargaining Program: Draft, Jul 1966 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Supervisors' Collective Bargaining Program: Final Draft, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Supplemental Agreement re: Increased Benefits of the Educational Fund, Sep 1, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Time and Leave Rules: as Amended by the 1978-80 Citywide Contract, Apr 2, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Tri-Partite Panel: Report and Related Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Union Preparation for Collective Bargaining, Nov 1967 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Union Representationd, 1966-1970, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - United Committee for Collective Bargaining, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Series IV: Grievances, Arbitrations and Legal Cases (General), 1953-1999
  - Arbitrations: General, 1968, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Arrest of Union Members, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Baldwin, Louis, Local 371, AFSCME, AFL-CIO v. Department of Welfare, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Blitz, Emily v. the City of New York et al, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Briefs in Support of: Legal Counsel, Relocations of East End Center, Departmental Emergency Time and Leave Rules, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Callahan, Robert et al (5 Homeless Men) v. Hugh L. Carey (Governor) et al and McCain et al v. Edward I. Koch (Homeless Families Case), 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - City of New York v. New York Local 246, SEIU: Decision No. B-16-69, Docket No. BCB-39-69, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - City of New York v. SSEU, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - City of New York v. SSEU: Case No. A-172-71, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - City of New York v. SSEU: Decision No. B-15-69, Docket No. BCB-47-69, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - City of New York v. SSEU et al, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Coleman, Richard et al v. Mitchell Ginsberg et al: Legal Documents and Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Commission on Human Rights on the Complaint of Shirley Anthony v. New York City Department of Social Services Associated Hospital Service, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Commission on Human Rights on the Complaint of Judith Rivera v. City of New York et al, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Commission on Human Rights on the Complaint of Linda Shah v. City of New York et al, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: AFSCME Judicial Panel, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1953-1959 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1960-1963 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1982-1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Grievances, Rebuttals and Requests, 1991-1996 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - DeGennaro, Matthew v. Jack R. Goldberg, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - DeMetro v. Ginsberg, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Department of Welfare, The City of New York: Charges and Specifications Relating to Jerome K. Hoffman, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Department of Welfare, The City of New York v. SSEU on behalf of Lexuis H. Harper, 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Department of Welfare, The City of New York v. SSEU on behalf of Alan R. Kalenberg, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Department of Welfare, The City of New York v. SSEU on behalf of B. R. Levine, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Ensley, Charles as President SSEU v. New York City Department of Personnel re: Article 78: Legal Briefs, Correspondence, Press Clippings and Related Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Ensley, Charles Individually and as President of Social Service Employees Union et al v. David N. Dinkins, as Mayor of the City of New York City et al, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Ensley, Charles as President of SSEU et al v. New York City Human Resources Administration: Affidavit of Charles Ensley, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - 14 BC Owners Corporation v. James Wertheim, 1990-1992 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Grievance Procedures, Related Correspondence and Materials, 1958-1974 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Harris, Charles Termination, 1990-1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Henderson, Dorrance M., Jr. v. Jules M. Sugarman, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Hernandez, Lydia et al v. Cesar A. Perales as Commissioner of the New York State Department of Social Services and William J. Grinker as Commissioner of New York City Department of Social Services, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Hughley, Otis v. Jack R. Goldberg, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Jackson, Isabel et al v. William J. Grinker and Cesar A. Perales, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Jeffreys, Arnold v. New York City Department of Personnel (includes Jimmy T. Handy v. City of NY Dept. of Pers.), 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Jones, James C. et al v. New York City Human Resources Administration et al, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Joseph and Josephine A. et al v. The New Mexico Human Services Department et al: Consent Decree re: Child Welfare Service Caseworkers, Undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, Thomas C. v. Jack R. Goldberg: Index Number 10,019/1969 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Local 371, SSEU v. The City of New York: Case No. A-564-76, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Lumpkin, Cleo B. et al v. Department of Welfare, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Marisol, A. et al v. Rudolph Giuliani et al, 1996-1998 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - McHugh, James v. Trustees SSEU Local 371 Education Fund, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - McKeon, James J. v. Trustees SSEU Local 371 and SSEU Local 371 v. McKeon, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Office of Labor Relations v. SSEU: Decision No. B-2-69, Docket No. BCB-26-68, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Office of Labor Relations v. SSEU: Decision No. B-10-68, Docket No. BCB-25-68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Office of Labor Relations v. SSEU: Docket No. BCB-13-68, Decision No. B-7-68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Office of Labor Relations v. SSEU: Docket No. BCB-14-68, Decision No. B-6-68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Office of Labor Relations v. SSEU: Docket No. BCB-15-68, Decision No. B-5-68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Padwee, Susan v. Local 371-SSEU et al, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Reynolds, Lakisha el al v. Rudolph Giuliani et al Memorandum and Order: Class Actions Complaint on Welfare Issues, Jan 25, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Ross, Elaine, Local 371 v. Department of Welfare, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Rudy, Zelda v. Jack R. Goldberg: Legal Documents, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Singer, Max v. Harry Bronstein and Jules Sugarman, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Snow, Raymond M. v. Jack R. Goldberg: Legal Documents, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - SSEU v. Justice Irving H. Saypol, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - SSEU v. Bill Schleicher: Case No. A68-175, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - SSEU v. the City of New York: Article 75 Suit to Compel Arbitration, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - SSEU v. the City of New York: Case No. A-68-69 (George Findlay, et al, Caseworkers at Gramercy Center), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - SSEU v. the City of New York: Case Nos. A-74-69 and A-74-69 (Pettiford and Behuniak), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - SSEU v. the City of New York: Case No. A-98-69 (Roth), 1971 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - SSEU v. the City of New York: Case No. A-174-71, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - SSEU v. the City of New York (Departments of Social Service and Juvenile Justice), 1987 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - SSEU v. the City of New York (Departments of Social Service and Juvenile Justice) re: Hours and Workweek of Houseparents, Opinion and Award, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - SSEU v. Department of Social Services, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Social Services Staff Men's Shelter v. Department of Social Services: Final Decision, Jun 13, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Sperling, Joseph et al v. George D. Clark and Clark v. Sperling, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Sperling, Joseph and James McKeon v. Julia Jorge et al and Jorge et al v. Sperling and McKeon, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Supervisor III Court Case, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Tepedino, Joseph et al v. James R. Dumpson: Legal Documents, Order Under Article 78, 1969-1972 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Trial Board Cases, 1960s (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Tutrone, Robert E. et al v. Department of Welfare, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Weller, Douglas (Caseworker): Pay Claim, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 39)